Hi!
In this video clip I will be showing you the final step in installing a smoke detector.
Next we need to install our battery.
You want to make sure you get the positive side to the positive side and negative side to the negative side.
Go and close the battery compartment.
At this point I like to test the smoke alarm while it is still on the ground.
I would hate to put it up in the ceiling and just to find out that it doesn't work because I would have to get back up there and take it down, so it is much easier to test it on the ground.
Everything seems to be working properly.
To install our smoke detector on to our base, we simply put it in place and rotate it clockwise until it snaps in place.
You might want to test it just to make sure that it is not loose.
Additionally it is always a good idea to test it one more time.